<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://magoja.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://magoja.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-09-01T17:45:11+00:00</updated><id>https://magoja.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Jake Util</title><subtitle>Personal engineering blog in creating JakeUtils, and other projectss and studies.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Beginning</title><link href="https://magoja.github.io/blog/2025/welcome/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Beginning"/><published>2025-08-26T02:39:32+00:00</published><updated>2025-08-26T02:39:32+00:00</updated><id>https://magoja.github.io/blog/2025/welcome</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://magoja.github.io/blog/2025/welcome/"><![CDATA[<p>There is always a beginning.</p> <p>One day, my wife was frustrated to find that a QR code she made for a school event required a subscription. She had already made a fancy board with it. Obviously, the site she was using was a QR code middleman site, and while they are running a legitimate business, most customers stumble into the “Expired QR code trap” unexpectedly. As you guessed, she was not interested in any of their services. There are too many traps like this on the internet. I want simple and easy tools to be accessible without these kinds of concerns.</p> <p>As an engineer, I know QR is a public tool that anyone can create easily without any service fees if you know software. I quickly made a tool for QR codes. By the way, AI tools these days are amazing. I started thinking this could be a fun side project.</p> <p>So here it is. I hope JakeUtil becomes a staple for many people for simple tasks. But please understand there could be bugs and missing features that might frustrate you. You can contribute! You can check anything I do in the GitHub repo. Feel free to submit a pull request.</p> <p>Thank you for visiting and reading this article.</p> <ul> <li>Jake</li> </ul>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="update"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is always a beginning.]]></summary></entry></feed>