<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://magoja.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://magoja.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2025-09-01T16:30:44+00:00</updated><id>https://magoja.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Jake Util</title><subtitle>Personal engineering blog in creating JakeUtils, and other projectss and studies.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Beginning</title><link href="https://magoja.github.io/blog/2025/welcome/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Beginning"/><published>2025-08-26T02:39:32+00:00</published><updated>2025-08-26T02:39:32+00:00</updated><id>https://magoja.github.io/blog/2025/welcome</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://magoja.github.io/blog/2025/welcome/"><![CDATA[<p>There is always a beginning.</p> <p>One day, my wife got frustrated to notice that a QR code that she made for a school event was asking for a subscription. She already made a fancy board with. Obviously the site she was using was a QRCode middle man site, which they are doing a legit business. However most of the customers stumbled in to the “Expired QR code trap” unexpectedly. You guessed she was not interested in any of their services. There are too many traps in the internet for this kind. I’d like to have simeple and easy stuff accessible without this kind of concerns.</p> <p>As an engineer, I know QR is a public tool that we can create easily without any service fees if you know software. I quickly made one tool for QR Code. Btw AI tools these days are amazing. I started thinking this could be a fun side project.</p> <p>So here it is. I hope this JakeUtil becomes a staple for many people for simple stuffs. But please understand there could be bugs, and missing features that make you frustrated. You can contribute! You can check anything that I do in the Github repo. Feel free to submit a pull request.</p> <p>Thank you for visiting and reading this article.</p> <ul> <li>Jake</li> </ul>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="update"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is always a beginning.]]></summary></entry></feed>